export default data = [
  {
      question: "Gorillas have often been portrayed as a fearful animal, but in truth these shy apes ______ fight over sex, food, or territory.",
      options: ["constantly","shortly","nearly","rarely"],
      correct_option: "rarely"
  },
  {
      question: "With her nine-to-five job, Sally sometimes has to run personal ______ during the lunch break, such as going to the bank or mailing letters.",
      options: ["affairs","errands","belongings","connections"],
      correct_option: "errands"
  },
  {
      question: "After an argument with the parents of his students, the teacher finally admitted his mistake and ______ himself to ask for their forgiveness.",
      options: ["resisted","humbled","detected","handled"],
      correct_option: "humbled"
  },
  {
      question: "Instead of criticizing other people, we should focus on their strengths and give them ______.",
      options: ["compliments","compromises","convictions","confessions"],
      correct_option: "compliments"
  },
  {
      question: "Taking advantage of a special function of the search engine, users can ______ the Internet without leaving behind any history of the webpages they visit.",
      options: ["browse","stride","rumble","conceal"],
      correct_option: "browse"
  },
  {
      question: "Due to extremely low rainfall and a dangerous reduction of reservoir water, the area is experiencing the worst ______ in 30 years. ",
      options: ["fluid","scandal","drought","nuisance"],
      correct_option: "drought"
  },
  {
      question: "On Teachers’ Day we pay ______ to Confucius for his contribution to the philosophy of education.",
      options: ["consent","tribute","devotion","preference"],
      correct_option: "tribute"
  },
  {
      question: "When the fire fighter walked out of the burning house with the crying baby in his arms, he was ______ as a hero by the crowd.",
      options: ["previewed","cautioned","doomed ","hailed"],
      correct_option: "hailed"
  },
  {
      question: "Due to the worldwide recession, the World Bank’s forecast for next year’s global economic growth is ______.",
      options: ["keen","mild","grim","foul"],
      correct_option: "grim"
  },
  {
      question: "Jeffery has always been a ______ person, so it’s not surprising he got into an argument with his colleagues.",
      options: ["respective ","preventive","contagious","quarrelsome"],
      correct_option: "quarrelsome"
  },
]